now let's talk about inspections so
现在让我们谈谈检查
inspections are similar to intentions in
检查类似于
a lot of ways they detect and correct
他们检测和纠正的很多方法
anomalous code as you're typing
键入时出现异常代码
sometimes they may not be displayed
有时它们可​​能不显示
inside the editor so you may have to
在编辑器中，因此您可能必须
invoke the inspections directly and you
直接调用检查，您
can do so by pressing alt shift I so if
可以通过按alt shift来做到这一点
you look inside the inspection profile
您在检查配置文件中查看
results for this particular file you'll
此特定文件的结果，您将
see that there are a few that are not
看到有一些不是
highlighted inside the editor so there
在编辑器中突出显示，因此
are a few that are I can simplify this
是我可以简化的几个
if condition for example but let's say
例如，如果有条件
let's take a look at some of these
让我们来看看其中的一些
declaration redundancies and so it looks
声明冗余，所以看起来
like this class can be declared packaged
像这样的类可以声明包装
local and so if I want to apply that
当地的，所以如果我想申请
then I can just right click and select
然后我可以右键单击并选择
make class package local since it isn't
将课程包设为本地，因为它不是
being used outside this package
在此包装之外使用
nice call IntelliJ so the second thing
很高兴打电话给IntelliJ，所以第二件事
is it uses the default file template I
它使用默认的文件模板吗
can choose to edit that template if I'd
可以选择编辑该模板
like using the velocity template
就像使用速度模板
language and once I apply this then will
语言，一旦我应用了
automatically add that to the file
自动将其添加到文件中
header you can run individual
您可以单独运行的标头
inspections by name as well by pressing
还要按名称检查
ctrl alt shift I and then typing the
ctrl alt shift I，然后输入
name of the inspection that you'd like
您想要的检查名称
to invoke I can specify the scope of the
调用我可以指定的范围
inspection and configure any file name
检查并配置任何文件名
filters that I'd like to add which will
我要添加的过滤器
automatically default to the source code
自动默认为源代码
extension for type of project we're
项目类型的扩展名
using let's take a look at some
让我们来看看一些
inspections that help us migrate between
检查，以帮助我们在
different language levels in Java so for
Java中的不同语言级别，因此
instance here I have the old Java syntax
我这里有旧的Java语法
for declaring an anonymous inner class
用于声明匿名内部类
and what I can do here is replace this
我在这里能做的就是替换这个
with a lambda and so this will
用lambda，所以这会
automatically refactor that for me
自动为我重构
and I can expand this to include an
我可以将其扩展为包括
expression body as well so this will
表达主体，所以这将
just add some braces what I can also do
只需加上一些括号我也可以做
is migrate away from loops by using the
通过使用
new streams in Java 8 so if I replace
Java 8中的新流，所以如果我替换
this with a for each loop then it'll
每个循环都有一个，然后
automatically refactor the code to use
自动重构代码以使用
the streams API another big feature in
Streams API的另一个重要功能
inspections are nullity inference and so
检查是无效推断，因此
if you call into some method that may
如果您调用某种可能
possibly return a null or is guaranteed
可能返回null或被保证
to never return a null then it will warn
永远不会返回空值，然后它将警告
me of that fact since this is always
我的事实，因为这总是
false if we navigate into this method
如果我们导航到此方法，则返回false
you can see that there's an annotation
您可以看到其中有一个注释
in the gutter right this will never
在排水沟里，这永远不会
return a null reference so here the ID
返回一个空引用，所以这里的ID
correctly informs me that this never
正确地告诉我，这永远不会
will be null and so I can remove that if
将为空，所以我可以删除它，如果
statement without any concern
声明无任何顾虑
additionally if there's a method that
另外，如果有一种方法
never expects the argument to be no but
从来没有期望这个论证是“否”
I've never explicitly told the compiler
我从未明确告诉编译器
that just based on the bytecode analysis
只是基于字节码分析
the IDE sees that the first thing is to
IDE看到的第一件事是
call some method on this argument here
在这里对此参数调用一些方法
then it will tell me that the argument
然后它会告诉我说
that I'm passing in is null and I don't
我传递的是null而且我不
need to do anything in order to get this
需要做任何事情才能得到这个
to work so for these and other
为这些和其他工作
inspections inside your IDE you can
您可以在IDE中进行检查
configure them on a project or default
在项目上配置它们或默认
level and if you can figure it on the
水平，如果你能找到它
project level it will be saved under
项目级别它将保存在
your project settings if you save it on
您保存的项目设置
a default level then they'll be saved
默认级别，然后将其保存
with your IDE settings so for all of
使用您的IDE设置，因此对于所有
these inspections there should be an
这些检查应该有一个
explanation or some sample code for you
说明或一些示例代码
to try out for more information about
尝试了解有关的更多信息
hundreds of code inspections available
数百种代码检查可用
in IntelliJ IDEA check out our getting
在IntelliJ IDEA中查看我们得到的
started page and don't forget to
开始页面，别忘了
subscribe to our blog at log JetBrains
在日志JetBrains上订阅我们的博客
comm slash idea
斜杠想法